# ABOUTME

I offer over 6 years of professional experience in software development.

Experience developing apps in different areas like accounting, retail, logistics, transport etc.

My goal is to keep learning and growing my career as a Full-Stack Software Engineer.

Programming is my passion. I also love working with cloud and infrastructure technologies.

# CONTACT

- atanasskambitovv@gmail.com
- +44 744 87 19 858 | +359 888 66 10 68
- https://github.com/NASOKILA
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/atanaskambitov-a69528162/

# EDUCATION

- SOUTH-WEST UNIVERSITY "NEOFIT RILSKI"
  Bachelor's degree in informatics
  15/09/2014 25/05/2018 (4 years)
- SOFTUNI "PRIVATE SOFTWARE UNIVERSITY"
  Graduated C# and JavaScript engineer
  05/12/2016 21/02/2018 (2 years)
- https://github.com/NASOKILA/Diplomas-Certificates

# ATANAS KAMBITOV SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Currently working in a small team of 5 people strictly following Agile ways of working using Scrum. Following on Solid Principles Design Patterns.

Big Fan of Refactoring, Pair Programming, BDD, TDD, Clean Code,
Clean Architecture, Component Design Principles and more...

## Auderli - United Kingdom, Brighton

#### **FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

15/11/2021 - NOW ( 1 YEAR )

#### Frontend development:

ReactJS, React Hooks, Typescript, Redux, BDD with Cucumber, Prettier, JS and TS Linters, Pre-commit hooks with Husky, Styled components and more... Testing with Jest & React Testing Library. Experience with CMS projects. Mainly with Gatsby, Netlify CMS and Bulma for styling.

Understanding of Mobile Development with React Native, using Expo both for IOS and Android apps.

#### **Backend Development:**

C# and .NET Core, using CQRS and Event Sourcing for managing events.

Working with EventStore, SQL, TSQL, Azure Cosmos and Redis Cache as databases.

Behavior Driven Development and Test Driven Development.

Testing with NUnit, XUnit & Specflow for specification testing (Given, When, Then). Using Assert First Technique Mocking objects with NSubstitute.

#### Cloud & Infrastructure as code:

Constantly working with Azure and Azure DevOps, managing YAML Pipelines, NuGet Packages as Artifacts, Repositories and deploying cloud resources.

Ability to raise entire infrastructure in Azure and AWS with HashiCorp Terraform.

Terraforming mainly VMs, Storage Accounts, AKS Clusters, WebApps, Containers, KeyVaults, Container Registries, SQL Databases, Traefik and more...

#### **External Services:**

Auth0 for user identity management.

HubSpot for CRM, marketing campaigns, marketing emails and analytics. Sentry for error Monitoring and Alerting.

GoDaddy for domain Registrations.

Figma for designing application components.

Google Tag Manager for Marketing/analytics and tags management.

Google Analytics & Heap and more...

# Sainsbury's – United Kingdom, Coventry

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

03/12/2018 - NOW (3.5 YEARS)

At Sainsbury's I worked on multiple projects mostly with C#, .Net Core, ReactJS, React Hooks, Redux, SQL, TSQL, EF Core, Dapper, MongoDB, Azure, AWS, S3, SNS, Lambda, DevOps, AKS, Docker, Signal R, Key vaults, AAD, Redis Cache, Container Registry, App Services, Azure Cosmos Db, Service Bus, Event Hubs, REST API's, SOAP, OOP and more.

Managing infrastructure using Terraform, CI/CD pipelines, container orchestration with Docker and Kubernetes cluster. Experience in Microsoft365, Azure, Microservice architecture, Cloud Native Apps, Full-stack development including Unit and Integration testing.

Usage of Power BI for reporting and Datadog for monitoring and alerting. Working in an agile way using scrum in a small team of five people providing quality, latency, stability and performance carefully following solid principles and design patterns.

## SoftUni – Bulgaria, Sofia

#### **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER**

#### 05/12/2016 - 21/12/2018 ( 2 YEARS )

Design and deliver backend RESTFULL API's using .NET Core and NodeJS + ExpressJS. Build and release frontend applications with ReactJS, Angular and Angular 2+. Experience with MVC, MVVM, REST, SOAP XML, JSON, YAML, Git, GitHub and more.

Optimizing SQL queries and working on relational databases with SQL, Dapper and EF Core. Quickly deliver quality code and meet deadlines on multiple projects using different technologies, languages and frameworks.

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### Badges:

https://aithub.com/NASOKILA/SoftUni/tree/master/Other/Badges



#### Diplomas:

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Diplomas-Certificates



#### Certificates:

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Diplomas-Certificates/tree/master/Certificates

#### PERSONAL PROJECTS

.NET Core

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Tangy-Restaurant

.NET Core and ReactJS

https://github.com/NASOKILA/todolist.backend https://github.com/NASOKILA/todolist.frontend

Angular

https://nasokila.github.io/comix-shop

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Portfolio-Projects/tree/comix-shop

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Agile Methodologies, Scrum, Cloud, Microservices, Serverless, Docker, C#, .NET Core, Node.js & Express.js, MVC & MVVM, RESTFUL APIs, SQL, Mongo DB, ReactJS, Angular, Redux, TypeScript, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, SOLID Principles, Design Patterns, HTML5 & CSS3, Less & Sass, Git, GitHub, Bitbucket.

Web Development, TDD, BDD, Cucumber, Prettier, JS and TS Linters, Husky, Styled components Jest, Enzyme, React Testing Library. Mobile Development, React Native, C#.NET Framework, .NET Core, ASP.NET, CQRS, Azure Functions, REST APIs, SOAP, OOP, Redis Cache, EventStore, NUnit, XUnit & Specflow, Selenium, Microsoft SQL Server, SQL, TSQL, MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Firebase, Kinvey.

AKS, EKS, CI/CD Pipelines, HashiCorp Terraform, AWS, S3, SNS, Lambda, Azure Signal R, Key vaults, AAD, Redis Cache, Container Registry, App Services, Azure Cosmos Db, Service Bus, Event Hubs., DevOps, Jira, XML, JSON, Agile, Scrum, Solid Principles, Design Patterns, Netlify CMS, Gatsby, WordPress, PrestaShop, SAS, Figma Designs, Postman.

External Services, Auth0, HubSpot, Sentry, GoDaddy, PowerBI, Figma, Google Tag Manager, Google Analytics, Datadog and more.

## **LANGUAGES**

ENGLISH | ITALIAN | SPANISH | BULGARIAN